[Music]
hello everyone and welcome to my little
corner of the world
today i wanted to do a cottage tour
since
so many people have requested to see
inside my home
[Music]
when i first moved in i took some time
to make it feel like a little piece of
wonderland
that i could escape to after work and
unleash my creativity
for me what makes my cottage special is
all the tiny little details
from making pressed flower art from my
walls
to even my little tea collection that i
have been growing this year
and of course my mini houseplants and
miniatures
even though it is a one-room cottage it
feels like the perfect size for me
i think that even if i had a family in
the future i wouldn't want a place that
much bigger
it is so easy to keep clean and tidy and
that makes me happy
since i'm capable of creating enormous
messes
especially in relation to my art
projects
you can see here that i've been painting
the walls i find it a wonderful
way to personalize the space
you may also notice that i'm obsessed
with books
i get them mostly secondhand but i did
used to work at a bookstore
if i could only recommend one to you it
would be the boy
the mole the fox and the horse it is a
hybrid
between a children's book and an adult
book and it is beautiful
to those who have inquired about my
wardrobe pretty much all of it has been
thrifted
or gifted to me by family members
[Music]
my bathroom actually doesn't have a sink
with running water but i get along just
well with a
pitcher and basin it's amazing how over
time with living this way
i've become accustomed to it and i don't
really need anything else to feel
comfortable
my boyfriend brings me crystals that he
has found out on his hikes in the
mountains
and i love to decorate my space with
them
[Music]
of course my favorite part of my cottage
is my art desk
it is where i like to sit and think up
all my new ideas for future projects
that is where i also keep some of my
favorite old books
it is so wonderful to hold a piece of
history in your hands
[Music]
as you can see this cottage is small and
simple i love to fill it with little
unusual pieces that i find at thrift
stores
or natural things that i find around my
property
i have so many plans to paint the walls
even more and
i hope you enjoyed looking around
[Music]
do
i decided not to do a garden tour since
many of my plants have been taken by the
autumn frost
however i have many plants next year to
grow a multitude
of herbs and flowers and i will
definitely share it with you then
[Music]
me
you